

Svetoslav Pandeliev

Technical Writer

WORK EXPERIENCE



USER ASSISTANCE DEVELOPER SAP Labs Bulgaria

Oct 2020 onwards

- Create and maintain developer tutorials.
- Prepare announcement and instructional videos for new documentation features.

effortel TECHNICAL WRITER Effortel Technologies SA

May 2018 to Sept 2020 (2 years 5 months)

- Draft user guides describing features of software products.
- Generate release notes (RN) in parallel with software releases
- Prepare arch and sequence diagrams, flowcharts, infographics, and other visuals.
- Review and edit UI strings.



PATENT SPECIALIST SAP Labs Bulgaria

Jan 2015 to Mar 2018 (3 years 3 months)

- Interview inventors about technical details of novel software solutions.
- Draft patent applications that cover technical aspects, UI look and feel, and functionality.

LIREX PRE-SALES ENGINEER Lirex BS

Feb 2013 to Dec 2014 (1 year 11 months)

- Analyze customer requirements and propose the right solution, based on technical specifications.
- Create detailed technical descriptions of provided solutions.



https://www.linkedin.com/in/svetoslav-pandeliev/



slavipande@gmail.com



+359-898-479892



svetoslavpandeliev.com

CLICK HERE FOR MY PORTFOLIO

SUMMARY

Curious tech writer with over 7 years of experience in translating complexity. Adept self-learner, accustomed to building up knowledge to ensure efficient communication with subject matter experts. Very good in understanding and successfully implementing new tools and technologies in day-to-day work.

SKILLS

- Excel in communication with individuals and small groups.
- Work harmoniously and effectively with others.
- Very good at analyzing information.
- Tech-savvy and quick to learn new programs.
- · Sensitive to deadlines.
- Track record of successfully handling multiple projects.
- English proficient user.
- German basic user.

EDUCATION HISTORY



MASTER DEGREE IN E-MANAGEMENT, E-GOVERNMENT
Technical University of Sofia, English Language Faculty of Engineering

Year of Graduation: 2015

BACHELOR OF COMPUTER SYSTEMS AND TECHNOLOGY (CST) Technical University of Sofia, Computer Systems Department

Year of Graduation: 2013